This is the most epic birthday party ever!
And an indoor sledding hill with axle-slap!
And I said all this up, surprised the world's most deserving kids.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
I'm important 3 months ago, one of these existed,
because that's when I reached out to a friend of mine
Oh, hey, Mark!
Phidias!
I'm planning on throwing the world's greatest birthday party
I can explain later.
For now, I need you to know what you've got in the idea.
That's a great question, Mark.
And as you can see, as long as you don't remove this screw,
You'll be fine.
You do realize that brings like seven laws of physics, right?
Well, we're working with cartoon physics,
, , , , , , , , ,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,
In the meantime, I was thinking Furb and I
why the hell would we both have our work cut out for us?
I'll talk to you later.  I'll talk to you later.
Now, I knew for personal experience
if you can pull off a finies-sum Furb invention in real life,
makes for a really epic party
15 tonnes de gelée à réserver.
When a human could endure.
So it was the first pass.
I just let two rockets with 2,500 Newtons-second total impulse
This is the test my hypothesis.
why finies-sum Furb is an animated show.
Tri,duo,one
That was the most powerful, defencing in history.
So to keep us from immediately spinning out of control,
and potentially losing all our dignity in the process,
Here we go.
And this time, let it rip.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
He can't keep his clothes on.
i think only one of them ignited.
So once we fix the fault to the ignition wire,
Go! Go!
No, no, no, no.
I can't! I can't! I can't!
How's he, Newton?
Which I'll remind you, ways more than I do.
completing the stylish dismount.
That was definitely both that time.
It's Tuesday, Ron!
And while the dual chain configuration did provide a lot more stability,
This is too squirrely.
We need to go to rigid chains.
Tri,duo,one
Go! Go!
️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️
It ripped our whole half-tuned steel swing structure out of the stakes,
You got-you got-
OK, well that's a successful rocket swing.
Now we just gotta figure out how to make it a little safer.
So we were off to a promising start.
We just needed a little more inspiration.
Hey, Mark, how's the build?
I feel, though, that the party needs a little something more.
I got it.
How about building on my backyard roller culture like the one we made at the beginning of summer?
♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪
For when they re-enter the atmosphere?
Yes, yes I am.
️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️
Oh, I gotta go.
Herb just arrived with.
Our store of the show.
No, Phineas, you don't need a tiny--
, Mark.
Oh, that's gonna get messy.
Roller coasters actually exist.
So I did what any self-respecting engineer would do as a first step and conducted some tedious research.
Now I knew that finding the perfect Goldilocks zone for our birthday guests would be critical.
Not so extreme, it sends him back to the hospital, but also not so boring, it feels like watching
William Austin video.
So armed with all the learnings from our TES research, we set up to build the perfect indoor roller
Coaster for my buddy Ethan.
About the way,this is Ethan.
And when you should know about Ethan, is he was recently diagnosed with a rare and severely
️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️
actually, his pain in nausea was so severe, he couldn't even walk from one room to another.
And after a full year, he'd recovered enough to make his way back to school.
And his luck would have it.
He not only had a birthday party coming up, but he was also a massive finish in Furb fan, which was
perfect because we had our first prototype of the world's greatest finish in Furb indoor roller
coaster ready to test.
Okay, man, here we go!
Let's go, let's go!
Oh yeah!
I think we're gonna have to check our calculations.
So I called some of my buddies who are really good at this.
And while not yet perfect, we were certainly on the right track.
Now we just needed a few more of them.
Good.  Good.
And things were going along great, but if I was going to get approval from the world's
So I took a closer look at their original coaster.
And while we definitely can't send even to France, we definitely could send them through
uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu
️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️
Our snakes bearing beautifully with a catapult calibrated mud bath.
That's why we're safety classes.
Why are you smiling so much?
o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o
️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️
Okey.
Clean as a whistle.
Oh, that's good.
So now it's both the roller coaster and the rocket is pretty much ready to go.
I opted for a check-in.
Hey, Mark, how's it going?
I mean, it's getting there.
But how do we really make this the best birthday party ever?
How about...
Swinter.
It's like summer, in winter.It's like summer, in winter.
All you need is a snilco maker and a bunch of jet-powered fans.
But make sure to keep it windows closed.
You really don't want to bring Swinter inside your house.
The news?
You pointed head of genius.
i think you're onto something.
Oh, that's right.
, while I have you, Urban Eye will wonder if your elephant prefers mint or bubble
️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️
Neither.
♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪
No, no, we don't.
OK, see you.
You know that.
Snowing indoors?
I'll make this be.
So I invited out an old friend to help.
Oh, my God.
This is insane.
Here is Fletcher.
And if you seem familiar to you, that's because five years ago I surprised
️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️
The best experiment.
Now, the time fletcher was dealing with a very rare form of brain cancer and since so many
I'm five years free of any signs of disease and I'm a senior in high school that's going
And you're almost as tall as me. And you're almost as tall as me.
I'm gonna say, I'm still taller. I'm gonna say, I'm still taller.
So I explained to him the engineering challenge of creating a non-cart tune indoors.
Snowstorm.
Fletcher was fine.
Let's do it.  Let's do it.
Yeah, the problem is I don't know how.
I don't have the...
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
With that uninspiring kick-off, we decided to just try some items we had lying around
I'm far the last one.
Our first thought was grading styrofoam, but it turns out that's not only dangerous.
uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu
Just created my finger.
️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️
But it turns out it's not very good for making so balls.
It's way too slippery.
And I'm gonna pop that.
The amount of diapers required would be half a metric, but which all left us with only
I am being 80,000 pounds of actual ice into a woodchomp.
I think it's going to work.
How's it feel to come in to check things out?
Okay, meat, what do you think?
It didn't take long for Flight sure to let the power go to his hand.
Mark,  ti si dobro?
Yeah, I'm fine.
But this is good or great.
Now that we had a solution in hand, I need to flex your help on one last finishing touch.
Oh, it was Nathan.
A
until later.
What?
Man, this is gonna take a while.
Much longer now with one person.
We're back in the snow!
Let's go! Let's go!
4 hours and 40 tons of ice later.
8 months of planning and where it comes down to this moment.
Here he is!
Oh my god, my heart is about to beat out of my chest.
We had either parents tell him he was auditioning for a toy commercial, so he wouldn't
Suspect anything.
We laid eyes on a balloon loaded indoor roller coaster, resting on two feet of fresh
No, no, no, no, no, no.
That's cold.
because he's been catching on fast.
Why is there a crunch load?
Nathan.
What's going on, pal?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I thought you might need a coat.
️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️
Finiessen's firm, probably.
Have you seen the episode where the make the rocket powered swing?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Have you seen the episode where they send the roller coaster to space?
Have you seen the episode Ethan called Swinter?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is Finiessen firm in real life.
I'm throwing you a birthday party today.
What?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You know what a banger party needs, Ethan?
A torta de cumpleaños?
He doesn't need a cake.
Let's work on a cake.
You know what it needs, though.
feel like we should have more people here.
You have friends you'd like to invite?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And that was the cue to send in.
All of Ethan's best friends.
As well as his loudest friends.
Ethan is a little sister, which meant that he had an important decision to make.
Ethan, to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to to
Ethan, our best to say yes.
Fine, but I have something to say.
OK,that was from you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What do you guys say?
We started the rocket swing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Your 104 days of summer vacation.
We won't look any further because it's here and it's called Camp Crunch Labs.
Camp Crunch Labs
With an eight-week virtual space theme summer camp that jumps to each of the planets in our solar system.
Featuring weekly videos with mega experiments that I do.
earns one of these bad boys to platinum ticket.
I'll tell you that usually the Crunch Labs bill boxes where they super fun toy together
️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️
We'll ship them to you every week.
Let's go. Let's go.
So if you want an eight-week summer camp where you could travel the cosmos while learning to
Think like an engineer.
️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️
Crunch Labs Crunch Labs Crunch Labs Crunch Labs Crunch Labs Crunch Labs Crunch Labs Crunch Labs Crunch Labs Crunch Labs Crunch Labs Crunch Labs Crunch Labs Crunch Labs Crunch Labs Crunch Labs Crunch Labs Crunch Labs Crunch Labs Crunch Labs Crunch Labs Crunch Crunch Crunch Crunch Crunch Crunch Crunch Crunch Crunch Crunch Crunch Crunch Crunch Crunch Crun
Starting first with the rockets.
You guys wanna see it.
️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️
Miss provided two advantages first.Miss provided two advantages first.Miss provided two advantages first.Miss provided two advantages first.
We learned from testing those big rockets.
We gave a lot of smoke.
But what's your breath?
Which is not ideal for your lungs or your smoke alarm.
️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️
Which is exactly what you naturally do when you pump your legs on a swing by the way.
Then you can add more and more energy to the swing.
Tell us enough.
Please clear the bar.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
And even with their modifications, he thought suddenly occurred.
That's a really dangerous.
️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️
Safety is for losers.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
See you as you with such a tough guy all of a sudden.
I decided to use Ethan to get a baseline.
Here we go.
Just seeing how high you could swing if you just had to rely on your boring old mussels.
Wow! Wow!
Ethan,
I shrimped.
Now, it was my turn to see what would have been if you added 14,000 RPM of propulsion.
Okay, are you guys ready?
Of course, the number one rule when demoing a potentially disastrous engineering bill that
I've never done this before.
What do you mean you've never done this before?
How has he been tested?
No, no, no, no.
Oh, my God!
That looks so nauseating.
ethan, eeeeee eeee!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
swim to break, starting with some snow cones.
And some snowballs.
However, unfortunately for them, certain habits--
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Headshot!
Who's next?
That was awesome!
Okey! Okey! Okey!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
And then suddenly, and very undeservedly, I might add.
I wasn't over my head.
why is everyone aiming at me?
Ok, je suis ?
Who wants to go sledding?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
!
Don't hide me!
I thought that was--
Ethan was really encouraging with his friends.
Soya!
That's when he was in the tackle.
Oh yeah!
Go back!
Phoenies and Furbin real life engineering build.
Now up the stakes, Ethan reminded me what their coaster was actually like in the show.
So if this is really Phoenies Furbin--
Oh yeah!
If this was Phoenies Furbin, it would be a triangle fair fair.
But I wasn't gonna make Ethan ride solo.
So I had no choice but to tie up.
I never met Phoenies and Furbin.
Oh yeah!
This was Phoenies Furbin.
So I had no choice but to tie up.
I've never met Ethan or you know this.
Tri!
Go! Go!
No, no, no, no.
And while the stakes were fake,
That's one of the stuff, of course.
So Mr. Rizzoff in Science Bob's 20 mile an hour car was.
No, no, no, no.
Nice and clean.
You won't have to shower tonight, at least.
I doubt that, but um.
So now that all three of our mentions were tested and Ethan approved.
Thank you. Thank you.
Music
ethan, et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et et
I didn't pull this off on my own.
What do you mean?
Hey, friends!
View what we've done!
No, you know for not relying on Cartoon physics, that looks so fun.
️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️
Now for the elephant toothpaste experiment.
Be sure firm isn't too close.
...................................................................................................
Wow, it looks like you got a lot of cleaning on your hand.
See?
️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️️
Bye, Mark.
Sorry, Ethan, but that trick won't work in real life.
m cleaning up? m cleaning up? m cleaning up?
Oh, my God.
. .
...................................................................................................
Now that Ethan has been given the best birthday ever,
why don't join us for the best summer-end.
Space Camp Crunchy-Lat.
8 weeks virtual space theme summer camp designed to help fight that summer
Since you got canned crunch locks off top of parents and a kind of a little bit of